A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the Vice President, Office Files of David Bell FA624
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Division Files, 1966 - 1981; I
  - Overseas Division Self-Study Files, E
    - OD Self-Study - General, 1966 - 1967 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - OD Self-Study - Ideas, 1966 - 1967 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - OD Self-Study - Log, 1966 - 1967 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - OD Self-Study - Representatives' Replies, 1966 - 1967 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - OD Self-Study - "0utsiders'" Replies, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - OD Self-Study - Summary of Replies, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - OD Self-Study - ID Meeting/Beirut Jan. 1967 - General, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - OD Self-Study - ID Meeting/Beirut Jan. 1967 - Agenda and Summary, 1966 - 1967 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - OD Self-Study - OD Basic Policy/Guidelines, 1966 - 1967 (Box 10, Folder 151)
- General Correspondence Files, 1966 - 1980; II
  Series II, Correspondence (1966-1980), contains correspondence generated by Mr. Bell during his years at the Foundation. Correspondents include Foundation colleagues and Trustees, Heads of State, ex-USAID colleagues, and grantee and other philanthropic organizations.
  This series is divided into the following two sub-series:
  A. Alphabetical Files (3 boxes)
  B. Chronological Files (7 boxes)
  - Alphabetical Files, 1966 - 1981; A
    These files consist of Bell's selected incoming and outgoing correspondence with Ford Foundation trustees and colleagues, grantee and membership organizations, and other donor organizations.
    These files are arranged alphabetically. Within each folder, correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - Bechtel, Stephen D., 1966 - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Botero, Rodrigo, 1978 - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Brimer, Andrew, 1974 - 1977 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Brookings Institution, 1967 - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1966 - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - Bundy, McGeorge - Speeches, 1967 - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Canadian International Development Research Centre (IDRC), 1969 - 1979 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), 1970 - 1977 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - CFR - Committee on Procedures, 1971 - 1972 (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - CFR - Nominating Committee, 1972 - 1973 (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - CFR - Nominating Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - CFR - Discussion Group on Foreign Aid Policy, 1966 - 1967 (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - CFR - Discussion Group on Foreign Aid Policy, 1967 - 1978 (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - CFR - Special Discussion Group: Vietnam's Post-Conflict Problems, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - CFR - Latin American Advisory Group (Nelson Rockefeller), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - CFR - Discussion Group on Multilateral Economic Development, 1969 - 1970 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - CFR - Study Group on American Aid Policy, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - CFR - Study Group on Transfer Of Technology, 1976 - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 169)
    - Dahrendorf, Ralph, 1975 - 1978 (Box 12, Folder 170)
    - Donaldson, William, 1976 - 1978 (Box 12, Folder 171)
    - Education and World Affairs (EWA), 1966 - 1974 (Box 12, Folder 172)
    - Ellis, James R., 1972 - 1980 (Box 12, Folder 173)
    - Ford, Henry II, 1966 - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 174)
    - "G" General Correspondence, 1969 - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 175)
    - Haas, Walter A., Jr., 1972 - 1978 (Box 12, Folder 176)
    - Heard, Alexander, 1968 - 1980 (Box 12, Folder 177)
    - Institute of International Education (IIE), 1967 - 1972 (Box 12, Folder 178)
    - International Association for Cultural Freedom (IACF), 1966 - 1975 (Box 12, Folder 179)
    - Islam, Nurul, 1973 - 1976 (Box 12, Folder 180)
    - Loudon, John H., 1967 - 1979 (Box 12, Folder 181)
    - Marshall, Dorothy N., 1974 - 1976 (Box 12, Folder 182)
    - Miller, J. Erwin, 1970 - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 183)
    - Overseas Development Council (ODC), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - Overseas Development Council (ODC), 1968 - 1980 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - ODC Meeting - May 20, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - ODC Meeting - October 30, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 187)
    - Perkins, Donald S., 1978 - 1980 (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - P. Peterson "Mission" February, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 189)
    - Rabb, Harriet, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 190)
    - Resources For The Future, 1968 - 1977 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, The, 1968 - 1980 (Box 13, Folder 192)
    - Soedjatmoko, Dr., 1975 - 1980 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - Spencer, Edson W., 1978 - 1981 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - Stevenson Institute, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - United Nations Development Programme, (UNDP), 1972 - 1973, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 196)
    - UN - Intergovt. - World Bank, 1966 - 1979 (Box 13, Folder 197)
    - UN - Intergovt. - World Bank - Employment Meeting, Feb. 1975 (Box 13, Folder 198)
    - United Nations International School, 1967 - 1969 (Box 13, Folder 199)
    - United Nations University, 1976 - 1980 (Box 13, Folder 200)
    - UN University - Human & Social Development Meeting, Tokyo, November 1975, 1975 - 1976 (Box 13, Folder 201)
    - UN University Meeting, Nov. 1975 - Background Papers, 1975 - 1977 (Box 13, Folder 202)
    - United States Agency for International Development (USAID), 1972 - 1980 (Box 13, Folder 203)
    - Wald, Patricia M., 1974 (Box 13, Folder 204)
    - Webster, Bethuel M., 1966 - 1970 (Box 13, Folder 205)
    - Wyzanski, Charles E., 1969 - 1972 (Box 13, Folder 206)
  - Chronological Files, 1966 - 1980; B
    These files consist of Bell's routine outgoing correspondence ("chrons") with Ford Foundation trustees and colleagues, grantee and membership organizations, other donor organizations, heads of state, and ex-USAID colleagues.
    These files are arranged chronologically. Within each year, they are arranged alphabetically.
    - Addressee, multiple, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 207)
    - AN - AT, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 208)
    - BA - BU, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 209)
    - CA - CL, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 210)
    - DA - DO, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 211)
    - FA - FR, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 212)
    - GA - GR, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 213)
    - HA - HU, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 214)
    - Islam, N., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 215)
    - JOH - JON, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 216)
    - KE - KU, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 217)
    - LE - LO, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 218)
    - MA - MY, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 219)
    - McC- McV, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 220)
    - NIE - NIM, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 221)
    - PA - PR, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 222)
    - RE - RO, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 223)
    - SC - SU, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 224)
    - TA - TR, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 225)
    - Umali, D. C., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 226)
    - WA - WO, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 227)
    - YO - ZU, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 228)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 229)
    - AD - AT, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 230)
    - BA - BU, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 231)
    - CA - CU, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 232)
    - DA - DU, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 233)
    - ED - EU, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 234)
    - FA - FU, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 235)
    - GA - GR, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 236)
    - HA - HU, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 237)
    - IL - IN, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 238)
    - JA - JO, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 239)
    - KA - KU, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 240)
    - LA - LY, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 241)
    - MA - MY, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 242)
    - McC - McR, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 243)
    - NA - NO, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 244)
    - OB - OW, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 245)
    - PA - PR, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 246)
    - RA - RU, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 247)
    - SA - SW, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 248)
    - TA - TY, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 249)
    - UD - UL, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 250)
    - VA - VO, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 251)
    - WA - WR, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 252)
    - YO - ZE, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 253)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 254)
    - AC - AT, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 255)
    - BA - BU, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 256)
    - CA - CU, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 257)
    - DA - DW, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 258)
    - EB - EV, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 259)
    - FA - FU, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 260)
    - GA - GR, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 261)
    - HA - HU, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 262)
    - JA - JO, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 263)
    - KE - KU, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 264)
    - LA - LO, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 265)
    - MA - MY, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 266)
    - McA - McN, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 267)
    - NA - NO, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 268)
    - OC - OW, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 269)
    - PA - PR, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 270)
    - RA - RU, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 271)
    - SA - SW, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 272)
    - TA - TV, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 273)
    - VAL - VAU, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 274)
    - WA - WO, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 275)
    - YA - YO, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 276)
    - ZEL - ZET, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 277)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 278)
    - AD - AV, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 279)
    - BA - BU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 280)
    - CA - CU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 281)
    - DA - DU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 282)
    - EC - EU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 283)
    - FA - FR, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 284)
    - GA - GU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 285)
    - HA - HU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 286)
    - Isard, W., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 287)
    - JA - JO, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 288)
    - KA - KR, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 289)
    - LE - LO, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 290)
    - MA - MY, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 291)
    - MacD - McN, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 292)
    - NA - NI, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 293)
    - 0'B - OL, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 294)
    - PA - PU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 295)
    - RA - RU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 296)
    - SA - SW, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 297)
    - TA - TU, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 298)
    - UD - UR, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 299)
    - VE - VO, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 300)
    - WA - WY, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 301)
    - XI - YO, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 302)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 303)
    - AD - AU, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 304)
    - BA - BU, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 305)
    - CA - CU, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 306)
    - DA - DU, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 307)
    - ED - EW, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 308)
    - FA - FU, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 309)
    - GA - GR, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 310)
    - HA - HU, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 311)
    - IS - IV, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 312)
    - JA - JO, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 313)
    - KA - KR, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 314)
    - LA - LY, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 315)
    - MA - MY, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 316)
    - MacD - McN, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 317)
    - NA - NO, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 318)
    - OL - OS, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 319)
    - PA - PS, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 320)
    - RA - RY, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 321)
    - SA - SW, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - TA - TU, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 323)
    - UC - VA, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 324)
    - WA - WO, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 325)
    - YU - ZW, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 326)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 327)
    - AD - AS, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 328)
    - BA - BU, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 329)
    - CA - CY, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 330)
    - DA - DR, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 331)
    - ED - EN, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 332)
    - FI - FU, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 333)
    - GA - GR, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 334)
    - HA - HU, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 335)
    - IL - IV, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 336)
    - JA - JO, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 337)
    - KE - KO, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 338)
    - LE - LO, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 339)
    - MA - McN, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 340)
    - NA - NU, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 341)
    - OC - OL, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 342)
    - PA - PR, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 343)
    - RA - RU, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 344)
    - SA - SY, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 345)
    - TA - TU, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 346)
    - UP - VO, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 347)
    - WA - WU, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 348)
    - XI - YU, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 349)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1972 August - December (Box 17, Folder 350)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1972 January - June (Box 17, Folder 351)
    - AD - AS, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 352)
    - BA - BU, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 353)
    - CA - CU, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 354)
    - DA - DY, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 355)
    - EC - EV, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 356)
    - FA - FU, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 357)
    - GA - GR, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 358)
    - HA - HU, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 359)
    - Ivy, J. T., 1972 (Box 17, Folder 360)
    - JA - JO, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 361)
    - KA - KO, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 362)
    - LE - LO, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 363)
    - MA - MO, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 364)
    - MacE - McN, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 365)
    - NE - NI, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 366)
    - O'D - OW, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 367)
    - PA - PS, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 368)
    - RE - RU, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 369)
    - SA - SW, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 370)
    - TA - TU, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 371)
    - UC - US, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 372)
    - VA - VO, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 373)
    - WA - WY, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 374)
    - ZE - ZW, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 375)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1973 August - December (Box 17, Folder 376)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1973 January - June (Box 17, Folder 377)
    - AL - AS, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 378)
    - BA - BU, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 379)
    - CA - CU, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 380)
    - DA - DR, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 381)
    - ED - EV, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 382)
    - FE - FU, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 383)
    - GA - GR, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 384)
    - HA - HU, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 385)
    - IL - IS, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 386)
    - JA - JO, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 387)
    - KA - KL, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 388)
    - LA - LO, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 389)
    - MA - MO, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 390)
    - MacE - McN, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 391)
    - NE - NI, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 392)
    - OK - OL, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 393)
    - PA - PU, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 394)
    - RE - RO, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 395)
    - SA - SU, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 396)
    - TH - TY, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 397)
    - Van de Velde, P. W., 1973 (Box 17, Folder 398)
    - WA - WY, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 399)
    - ZE - ZI, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 400)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1974 July - December (Box 18, Folder 401)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1974 January - May (Box 18, Folder 402)
    - AH - AR, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 403)
    - BA - BU, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 404)
    - CA - CY, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 405)
    - DA - DY, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 406)
    - EB - EM, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 407)
    - FI - FU, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 408)
    - GA - GR, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 409)
    - HA - HU, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 410)
    - IL - IS, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 411)
    - JA - JO, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 412)
    - KA - KW, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 413)
    - LA - LO, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 414)
    - MA - MU, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 415)
    - MacL - McN, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 416)
    - NE - NI, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 417)
    - OK - OL, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 418)
    - PA - PO, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 419)
    - Qureshi, M. L., 1974 (Box 18, Folder 420)
    - RA - RU, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 421)
    - SA - SU, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 422)
    - TRO - TRU, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 423)
    - VA - VI, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 424)
    - WA - WO, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 425)
    - YA - ZE, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 426)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1975 July - December (Box 18, Folder 427)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1975 January - June (Box 18, Folder 428)
    - AH - AR, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 429)
    - BA - BU, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 430)
    - CA - CY, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 431)
    - DA - DR, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 432)
    - ED - EL, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 433)
    - FI - FO, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 434)
    - GL - GR, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 435)
    - HA - HU, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 436)
    - Ivy, J. T., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 437)
    - Johnson, A. A. - Johnson, H. G., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 438)
    - KA - KR, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 439)
    - LE - LO, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 440)
    - MA - MI, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 441)
    - McG - McN, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 442)
    - NA - NI, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 443)
    - 0'B - OH, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Perkins, J. A., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - RI - RU, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - SC - SW, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - TH - TU, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - VA - VO, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - WA - WY, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - YA - ZA, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1976 July - December (Box 19, Folder 452)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1976 January - June (Box 19, Folder 453)
    - Adil, A., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 454)
    - BA - BU, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - CA - CY, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 456)
    - DA - DR, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 457)
    - EA - EL, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 458)
    - FA - FU, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 459)
    - GA - GW, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 460)
    - HA - HU, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 461)
    - IL - HU, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 462)
    - Joseph, S. C. - Josephson, M., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 463)
    - KE - KO, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 464)
    - LE - LY, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 465)
    - MA - MO, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 466)
    - MacD - McP, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 467)
    - NI - NO, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 468)
    - OL - OY, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 469)
    - PA - PS, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 470)
    - RE - RO, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 471)
    - SA - SZ, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 472)
    - TA - TY, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 473)
    - WA - WO, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 474)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1977 July - December (Box 19, Folder 475)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1977 January - June (Box 19, Folder 476)
    - AL - AS, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 477)
    - BA - BU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 478)
    - CA - CU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 479)
    - DA - DY, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 480)
    - ED - ES, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 481)
    - FI - FU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 482)
    - GA - GW, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 483)
    - HA - HU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 484)
    - IN - IS, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 485)
    - KA - KY, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 486)
    - LE - LU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 487)
    - MA - MO, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 488)
    - McG - McN, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 489)
    - NA - NI, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 490)
    - PA - PO, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 491)
    - RO - RU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 492)
    - SA - SU, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 493)
    - TA - TR, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 494)
    - Van Wyk, F., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 495)
    - WH - WO, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 496)
    - ZAB - ZAF, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 497)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1978 July - December (Box 19, Folder 498)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1978 January - June (Box 19, Folder 499)
    - Agrawal, O. P., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 500)
    - BA - BU, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 501)
    - CA - CU, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 502)
    - DA - DY, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 503)
    - EY - FU, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 504)
    - GA - GR, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 505)
    - HA - HU, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 506)
    - Jaffe, F. S., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 507)
    - KA - KR, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 508)
    - LE - LY, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 509)
    - MA - MAC, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 510)
    - NG - NI, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 511)
    - PE - PET, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 512)
    - RA - RO, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 513)
    - SC - SZ, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 514)
    - TH - TU, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 515)
    - VA - VU, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 516)
    - WA - WI, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 517)
    - ZE - ZI, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 518)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1979 July - December (Box 20, Folder 519)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1979 January - June (Box 20, Folder 520)
    - BA - BU, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 521)
    - CA - CO, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 522)
    - DE - DU, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 523)
    - ED - EY, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 524)
    - FA - FU, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 525)
    - GE - GR, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 526)
    - HA - HU, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 527)
    - J0 - KR, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 528)
    - LA - LO, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 529)
    - MA - ME, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 530)
    - NE - NI, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 531)
    - OS - PS, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 532)
    - RA - RU, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 533)
    - SC - SU, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 534)
    - TE - TR, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 535)
    - VO - WR, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 536)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1980 July - December (Box 20, Folder 537)
    - Addressee, multiple, 1980 January - June (Box 20, Folder 538)
    - Antrobus, P., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 539)
    - BE - BU, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 540)
    - CA - CO, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 541)
    - Dressner, H. R., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 542)
    - ED - EM, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 543)
    - FI - FU, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 544)
    - GA - GR, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 545)
    - HA - HU, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 546)
    - IK - IV, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 547)
    - JA - JO, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 548)
    - KE - KO, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 549)
    - LA - LO, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 550)
    - MA - MU, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 551)
    - PE - PU, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 552)
    - RA - SW, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 553)
    - TE - TH, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 554)
    - WA - YA, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 555)
- Trustee Meeting Files, 1966 - 1980; III
  Series III, Trustee Meeting Files (1966-1980), contains material on the meetings of the Board of Trustees and its subcommittees: the International, Executive, Finance, and Communications Committees. Of particular interest are Bell's rough notes summarizing the meetings.
  The folders are arranged chronologically by date of meeting. Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse chronological order. Files of the Board of Trustees meetings on a given date precede those of the subcommittees.
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 23-24, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 556)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 28- 29, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 557)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 8-9, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 558)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 30-31, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 559)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 29-30, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 560)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 28-29, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 561)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 7-8, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 562)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 28-29, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 563)
  - International Subcommittee Meeting, Mar. 27, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 564)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 27-28, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 565)
  - International Subcommittee Meeting, June 26, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 566)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Sept. 26-27, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 567)
  - International Committee Meeting Sept. 26, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 568)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 13-14, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 569)
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 12, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 570)
  - Supplemental Funds for Population, FY 1969, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 571)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 27-28, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 572)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 26, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 573)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, May 28, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 574)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 26-27, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 575)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 25, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 576)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 25-26, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 577)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 24, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 578)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Nov. 13, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 579)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 12-13, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 580)
  - International Committee Meeting, Dec. 11, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 581)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Feb. 24, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 26-27, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 583)
  - International Committee Meeting, Mar. 25, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 584)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, May 28, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 585)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 25/26, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 586)
  - International Committee Meeting, June 23, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 587)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Sept. 24-25, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 588)
  - International Committee Meeting, Sept. 23, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 589)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec. 11-12, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 590)